Guide to the Montana Legislative Council Records 1955-1983
Montana Historical Society
- Subject Files
  - Interim Study Committee on State Mandates and the effects of state owned property on local governments, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 16 / 9-10)
  - Subcommittee on State Printing, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 16 / 11)
  - Subcommittee on Subdivision Laws, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 16 / 12-13)
  - Subcommittee on Subdivision Laws: correspondence, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 16 / 14)
  - Subcommittee on Subdivision Laws: minutes, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 16 / 15-17)
  - Governor's Special Committee on Taxation, 1955 (Box-folder 16 / 18-20)
  - Subcommittee on Taxation, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 17 / 1-5)
  - Subcommittee on Taxation (re corporation license tax), 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17 / 6-7)
  - Subcommittee on Taxation (re household goods, property taxes), 1973 (Box-folder 17 / 8)
  - Subcommittee on Taxation (re inheritance tax), 1975-1977 (Box-folder 17 / 9)
  - Subcommittee on Taxation (re moneys, solvent credits, and industrial facilities taxation), 1974 (Box-folder 17 / 10)
  - Subcommittee on Taxation (re property taxation), 1959-1961 (Box-folder 17 / 11)
  - Subcommittee on Taxation (re property taxes: assessment and classification, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 17 / 12-14)
  - Subcommittee on Taxation (re state income tax), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 17 / 15)
  - Subcommittee on Taxation (re vehicle licensing and taxation), 1974 (Box-folder 17 / 16-17)
  - Joint Subcommittee on Transportation (re rail line abandonment, air service, transportation of commodities, etc.), 1981-1982 (Box-folder 17 / 18-19)
  - Subcommittee on University - School Equalization - Juvenile Institutions, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 17 / 20)
  - Subcommittee on Vietnam Veteran Bonus, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 17 / 21)
  - Subcommittee on Vocational Education, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 17 / 22)
  - Subcommittee on Vocational Education, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 18 / 1)
  - Subcommittee on Water and Self Insurance: see Subcommittee on Self-Insurance (Box-folder 18 /)
  - Subcommittee on Water Conservancy Districts, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 18 / 2-3)
  - Water Resources and Adjudication Oversight Committee, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 18 / 4-6)
  - Subcommittee on Water Resources Board, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 18 / 7)
  - Water Resources Oversight Committee, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 19 / 1)
  - Subcommittee on Water Rights (determination of existing water rights), 1977-1979: see Box 20 folders 1-19 (Box-folder 19 /)
  - Subcommittee on Water Use Priorities, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 19 / 2-3)
  - Subcommittee on Water Use Priorities (re uses of water for the development of coal resources), 1967-1968 (Box-folder 19 / 4)
  - Select Committee on Wild Rivers, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 19 / 5-6)
  - Select Committee on Wine and Liquor Retailing, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 19 / 7)
  - Subcommittee on Workmen's Compensation, 1974 (Box-folder 19 / 8)
  - Subcommittee on Water Rights (determination of existing water rights), 1977-1979 (Box-folder 20 / 1-19)
  - Montana Salary Commission (report and recommendations), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 20 / 20-29)